Guide to Danbury's Third Century Research Collection MS 058
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- Interviews, 57706
  - Jack Murphy/Hugh Morgan, November 7, 2008 (Box 6)
    Discussion includes: his life, growing-up in Danbury, leaving for college, dating his future wife, returning to Danbury after college.
  - Sam Hyman, May 20, 2008 (Box 6)
    Discussion includes: coming to Danbury from NYC, Danbury Hospital Leadership in NAACP, description of Dr. Adams, Gino Arconti, role of churches, Hord Foundation and other Afro-American leadership group, NAACP issues and tactics, Marcus Dairy.
  - Rabbi Malino, November 20, 1998 (Box 6)